Pretty obvious spoilers.
I was excited for a lesbian movie set in my beautiful city. They had so much to work with, and yet they did nothing with it. The plot was cliché and overused, and somehow, even then, minuscule. The acting was embarrassing. I wanted to like Erika Linder because she's beautiful and she has perfect eyes, but no one in this movie could act to save their lives. The dialogue was pitiful. I think I have watched D list horror flicks with better dialogue.
Nice, simple story, about two girls, who fall in love. What is great about this movie, is the chemistry between Erika Linder and Natalie Krill. Both ladies are absolutely terrific. Especially Erika Linder. She is a model, not a professional actres, but her charisma is undeniable. Btw, the erotic scenes are hot, but intimate. I wish both ladies A list carrer, because they deserve it. 
So many missed opportunities to make this a decent film! What a horrible waste of time! I'm glad I watched this movie online instead of going to the movie theater. They tried to make this film erotic and edgy, and they failed at that too. It wasn't even sexy. Okay, maybe the movie poster and trailer were... 🙁
I am not knowledgeable enough of the complexity of lesbian relationships to measure the depth in which this film explores there, and the film seems to invite the viewers there. But I find this film quite exceptional for creating such a vigorous attraction between the two woman characters, and for their acting performance giving birth to two totally elaborated and different personalities,
This movie is very graphic. It is about a very passionate and honest lesbian who breaks up with her long-term relationship because she believes she is toxic to her because she does not love her the way the other loves her. In a way this is both cruel and honest. It is not very accommodating to the feelings of the girlfriend, who shows signs of disgust, hurt and utter alienation. This break-up scene which sets the stage for the whole movie is significant. Lesbian movies often do not make the big screen theaters, so this one slipped through the cracks, in my opinion. In a way, Dallas, the lead female actress, is a very cold and calculated person
This film should be commended for its stark and unforgiving portrayal of Female longing, passion and Love. Though the dialogue can be predictable at times and the storyline is nothing new, the actors bring a deep sensitivity to their roles. Erika Linder's Dallas, as the out lesbian, is a character of silent brooding, prone to fits of sensual passion. Natalie Krill's Jasmine, is a Well-to-do Fashion Editor who is caught up in a lesbian romance for the first time.
Loved this movie. The storyline was great. The acting superb. The sex scenes VERY REALISTIC. I wish more movies like this would be made in English. You can find a lot like it foreign made. Time for the United States to catch up. The love story was convincing. Can't wait to buy it on DVD.